

(604) 349-4363

nspanos@sfu.ca

nspanosportfolio.com

Who am I?

I am a relaxed yet driven Interactive Arts and Technology student who loves to create products through ideative and iterative processes. Through my experiences, I have developed strong communication skills and am an effective team player. Outside of work I am an active boxer, coach, and hockey player who loves to compete.

Skills Technical Design **Process** Machine Tools Illustrator Photoshop Ideation Prototyping Java Copywriting Microsoft OfficeHand Tools ○ HTML & CSS ○ Indesign Sketching - Excel, Word - For prototyping

Design Experience



Summer 2018

Role: Project Manager // Primary Fabricator // Copywriter

Context: Final project where my group and I designed and built a VR headset similar to Google Cardboard. Aside from the headset, the deliverables were to create a final presentation on the features and design intent. I designed the mechanisms for the headset, built it, and wrote copy for the final presentation. The end result was a final grade of an A in the course.

- Tasks: Project manager: time and team management
 - Researched and identified target audience and relevant materials
- Ideated & prototyped multiple iterations
- Used various fabrication techniques to create and finish different parts of the headset

+ Narrative Design - Group Project from Narrative in New Media

Fall 2019

Role: Project Manager // Script Writer

Context: Final project of the course where my group designed and created a visual novel set during World War I with a branching narrative. The goal was to explore creative writing with multiple outcomes to produce a compelling narrative with written and visual aspects. The end result was a grade of A on the project and the professor is using it as an example for future students of the course.

- Tasks Managed timeline for the completion of project milestones
 - Worked collaboratively with the team to create the premise for the project and its major elements
- Wrote the script including transitions and scenes specifically for the visual novel medium
- Assisted in areas where the team needed help to complete on schedule



(604) 349-4363

nspanos@sfu.ca

nspanosportfolio.com

Work Experience



🙀 North Shore Racks

May 2019 - August 2019

Role: Assembler

Context: Part of an assmbly crew building high quality bike racks. Building process was geared toward assembling as many racks with the fewest mistakes in as short a time possible

Tasks: • Assembled multiple parts at a time efficiently Skills Gained: • Ability to work smoothly in a team, handing off each finished part in a timely manner Quality control for each part assembled



Griffins Boxing & Fitness

September 2018 - August 2019

Role: Assistant Boxing Coach

Context: Worked with a full coach in running drills and exercises to train lower level boxer in helping them boost their confidence in their technique and physique. Able to lead classes in place of head coach.

Skills Gained: • Became a strong communicator in relaving Tasks: • Demonstrate techniques in a clear manner

 Work with youth and adults Enhanced inter-personal skills



Grouse Mountain

October 2015 - December 2016

Role: Base Operations // Grounds Personnel

Context: Grounds crew helping guests with any issues or questions and maintaining smooth transfers of people on the trams. Awarded employee of the month after intense windstorm grounded trams and left 200 people stranded on the hill overnight.

Tasks: • Helped thousands of people onto the hill

Skills Gained: • Developed my calm & professional demeanor

instructions to students

 Maintaining base facilities and interacting with guests

 Experiencedin conflict management working with the public

Education

Simon Fraser University - School of Interactive Arts & Technology Fall 2016 - Present

Major: Bachelor of Arts // Design Concentration

Details: Unique program that provides students with a range of technical, design and written skills. This invaluable training and knowledge combined with my work experience makes me a well-rounded individual.

Interests



Hockey

Hockey is a huge part a my life and I've playing since I was a kid to now as an adult, hopefully with no end in sight.



Video games have been a great source of enjoyment, from playing with friends to solo adventures it is a total blast.



Building and painting models is when I can truly relax and slow down from everyday life. A meditative experience best describes it.